<quotes>
<topic>Character Building Quotations</topic>
<quote>
<text>You cannot dream yourself into a character; you must hammer and forge yourself one.</text>
<authby>Henry David Thoreau</authby>
</quote>
<quote>
<text>Be your character what it will, it will be known, and nobody will take it upon your word.</text>
<authby>Lord Chesterfield</authby>
</quote>

<quote>
<text>Reputation is for time; character is for eternity.</text>
<authby>J. B. Gough</authby>
 </quote>
<quote>
<text>Nothing of character is really permanent but virtue and personal worth.</text>
<authby>Daniel Webster</authby>
</quote>
<quote>
<text>Character is like a tree and reputation is like its shadow. The shadow is what we think of it; the tree is the real thing.</text>
<authby>Abraham Lincoln</authby>
</quote>
<quote>
<text>Parents can only give good advice or put them on the right path, the the final forming of a person's character lies in their own hands.</text>
<authby>Anne Frank</authby>
</quote>
<quote>
<text>The essential thing is not knowledge, but character.</text>
<authby>Joseph Le Conte</authby>
</quote>
<quote>
<text>The great hope of society is individual character.</text>
<authby>William Ellery Channing</authby>
</quote>
<quote>
<text>A good name will shine forever. </text>
<authby>Proverb</authby>
</quote>
<quote>
<text>A fair reputation is a plant, delicate in its nature, and by no means rapid in its growth. It will not shoot up in a night like the gourd of the prophet; but, like that gourd, it may perish in a night.</text>
<authby>Jeremy Taylor</authby>
</quote>
<quote>
<text>Talents are best nurtured in solitude. Character is best formed in the stormy billows of the world. </text>
<authby>Johann Wolfgang Von Goethe</authby>
</quote>
<quote>
<text>Our character is but the stamp on our souls of the free choices of good and evil we have made through life.</text>
<authby>John C. Geikie</authby>
</quote>
<quote>
<text>Character is a diamond that scratches every other stone.</text>
<authby>Cyrus A. Bartol</authby>
</quote>
<quote>
<text>It matters not what you are thought to be, but what you are.</text>
<authby>Publilius Syrus</authby>
</quote>
<quote>
<text>In the stormy current of life characters are weights or floats which at one time make us glide along the bottom, and at another maintain us on the surface.</text>
<authby>Hippolyte Taine</authby>
</quote>
<quote>
<text>Character is what you think in the dark.</text>
<authby>Dwight L. Moody</authby>
</quote>
<quote>
<text>Character is the real foundation of all worthwhile success.</text>
<authby>John Hays Hammond</authby>
</quote>
<quote>
<text>Nature magically suits a man to his fortunes, by making them the fruit of his character.</text>
<authby>Ralph Waldo Emerson</authby>
</quote>

<quote>
<text>Characters do not change. Opinions alter, but characters are only developed.</text>
<authby>Benjamin Disraeli</authby>
</quote>
<quote>
<text>A man's character is like his shadow, which sometimes follows and sometimes precedes him, and which is occasionally longer, occasionally shorter, than he is.</text>
<authby>Madame de la Rochejuquelein</authby>
</quote>
<quote>
<text>Do what you know and perception is converted into character. </text>
<authby>Ralph Waldo Emerson</authby>
</quote>

<quote>
<text>Men best show their character in trifles, where they are not on their guard. It is in the simplest habits, that we often see the boundless egotism which pays no regard to the feelings of others and denies nothing to itself.</text>
<authby>Arthur Schopenhauer</authby>
</quote>
<quote>
<text>Every man, as to character, is the creature of the age in which he lives. Very few are able to raise themselves above the ideas of their times.</text>
<authby>Voltaire</authby>
</quote>
<quote>
<text>It is of little traits that the greatest human character is composed. </text>
<authby>William Winter</authby>
</quote>
<quote>
<text>Character is perfectly educated will.</text>
<authby>Novalis</authby>
</quote>
<quote>
<text>Character is the result of two things: Mental attitude and the way we spend our time.</text>
<authby>Elbert Green Hubbard</authby>
</quote>
<quote>
<text>Character and personal force are the only investments that are worth anything.</text>
<authby>Walt Whitman</authby>
</quote>

<quote>
<text>Every thought willingly contemplated, every word meaningly spoken, every action freely done, consolidates itself in the character, and will project itself onward in a permanent continuity.</text>
<authby>Henry Giles</authby>
</quote>
<quote>
<text>Character is, for the most part, simply habit become fixed. </text>
<authby>C. H. Parkhurst</authby>
</quote>
<quote>
<text>We are builders of our own characters. We have different positions, spheres, capacities, privileges, different work to do in the world, different temporal fabrics to raise; but we are all alike in this, -- all are architects of fate.</text>
<authby>John Fothergill Waterhouse Ware</authby>
</quote>
<quote>
<text>Character is, in the long run, the decisive factor in the life of individuals and of nations alike. </text>
<authby>Theodore Roosevelt</authby>
</quote>
<quote>
<text>Actions, looks, words and steps form the alphabet by which you may spell character. </text>
<authby>Johann Kasper Lavater</authby>
</quote>
<quote>
<text>Every human being is intended to have a character of his own; to be what no others are, and to do what no other can do.</text>
<authby>William Henry Channing</authby>
</quote>
<quote>
<text>Let us not say, Every man is the architect of his own fortune; but let us say, Every man is the architect of his own character.</text>
<authby>George Dana Boardman</authby>
</quote>
<quote>
<text>Fate is character. </text>
<authby>William Winter</authby>
</quote>
<quote>
<text>Character is higher than intellect. A great soul will be strong to live, as well as strong to think. </text>
<authby>Ralph Waldo Emerson</authby>
</quote>
</quotes>