<quotes><topic>Communication Quotations</topic>
<quote>
<text>Be silent, or say something better than silence.</text>
<authby>Pythagoras </authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Proper words in proper places make the true definition of a style.</text>
<authby>Jonathan Swift</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>It is as easy to draw back a stone, thrown with force from the hand, as to recall a word once spoken.</text>
<authby>Menander</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Many can argue - not many converse. - A. Bronson Alcott</text>
<authby>outline of two women in a disagreement</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Much tongue and much judgment seldom go together.</text>
<authby>Roger L'Estrange</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Good communication is as stimulating as black coffee, and just as hard to sleep after.</text>
<authby>Anne Morrow Lindbergh</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Have something to say, say it, stop talking.</text>
<authby>George Horace Lorimer</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>If the truth were self evident, eloquence would be unnecessary.</text>
<authby>Cicero</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>We never listen when we are eager to speak.</text>
<authby>François de La Rochefoucauld</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>He that converses not, knows nothing.</text>
<authby>English Proverb</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>It is good to rub and polish our brain against that of others. </text>
<authby>Montaigne</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Grant that we may not so much seek to be understood as to understand.</text>
<authby>Saint Francis of Assisi</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Be silent and pass for a philosopher.</text>
<authby>Latin Proverb</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>My words fly up, my thoughts remain below: Words without thoughts, never to heaven go.</text>
<authby>William Shakespeare, Hamlet. Act III. Sc. 3</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>People who have nothing to say are never at a loss in talking.</text>
<authby>Josh Billings</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Deliver your words not by number but by weight.</text>
<authby>Proverb</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>I saw one excellency that was within my reach —it was brevity; and I determined to obtain it.</text>
<authby>William Jay</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>The great thing is to know when to speak and when to keep quiet.</text>
<authby>Seneca the Younger</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Silence is often advantageous.</text>
<authby>Menander</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Eloquence is the power to translate a truth into language perfectly intelligible to the person to whom you speak.</text>
<authby>Ralph Waldo Emerson</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Language is the close-fitting dress of thought.</text>
<authby>R. C. Trench</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Good, the more communicated, more abundant grows.</text>
<authby>John Milton</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Silence is one great art of conversation. </text>
<authby>William Hazlitt</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>The first ingredient in conversation is truth: the next good sense; the third, good humor; and the fourth wit.</text>
<authby>Sir William Temple</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>True eloquence, indeed, does not consist in speech. It cannot be brought from far. Labor and learning may toil for it, but they will toil in vain. Words and phrases may be marshalled in every way, but they cannot compass it. It must exist in the man, in the subject, and in the occasion.</text>
<authby>Daniel Webster</authby>
</quote>
</quotes>