<quotes><topic>Dealing with People</topic>
<quote>
<text>You must look into other people as well as at them.</text>
<authby>Lord Chesterfield</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>A man's own good breeding is the best security against other people's ill manners.</text>
<authby>Lord Chesterfield</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>The secret of many a man's success in the world resides in his insight into the moods of men and his tact in dealing with them.</text>
<authby>J. G. Holland</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>There is a grace of kind listening, as well as a grace of kind speaking.</text>
<authby>Frederick William Faber</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>To rejoice in another's prosperity, is to give content to your own lot: to mitigate another's grief, is to alleviate or dispel your own. </text>
<authby>Thomas Edwards</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Hear the meaning within the word.</text>
<authby>William Shakespeare</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Charity, good behaviour, amiable speech, unselfishness — these by the chief sage have been declared the elements of popularity. </text>
<authby>Burmese Proverb</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Kind words are the music of the world. </text>
<authby>F. W. Faber</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Nothing is ever lost by courtesy. It is the cheapest of pleasures, costs nothing, and conveys much.</text>
<authby>Erastus Wiman</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>What you do not want done to yourself, do not do to others.</text>
<authby>Confucius</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>We are far more liable to catch the vices than the virtues of our associates.</text>
<authby>Denis Diderot</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Arguing with a fool proves there are two. </text>
<authby>Doris M. Smith</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Be courteous to all, but intimate with few; and let those be well-tried before you give them your confidence. </text>
<authby>George Washington</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Look to be treated by others as you have treated others.</text>
<authby>Publilius Syrus</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>I have made it a rule never to be with a person ten minutes without trying to make him happier.</text>
<authby>Various Attributions</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Success in life, in anything, depends upon the number of persons that one can make himself agreeable to.</text>
<authby>Thomas Carlyle</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Never part without loving words to think of during your absence. It may be that you will not meet again in this life.</text>
<authby>Jean Paul Richter </authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Let us believe neither half of the good people tell us of ourselves, nor half of the evil they say of others.</text>
<authby>J. Petit Senn</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>The more you say, the less people remember.</text>
<authby>François Fénelon</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>You know what charm is: a way of getting the answer yes without having asked any clear question.</text>
<authby>Albert Camus</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Never lose a chance of saying a kind word.</text>
<authby>William Thackeray</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>The soul of conversation is sympathy.</text>
<authby>Thomas Campbell</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>It is always good to know, if only in passing, charming human beings. It refreshes one like flowers and woods and clear brooks.</text>
<authby>George Eliot</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>The most important single ingredient in the formula of success is the knack of getting along with people.</text>
<authby>Theodore Roosevelt</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Every man is a volume if you know how to read him.</text>
<authby>William Ellery Channing</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Learn to regard the souls around you as parts of some grand instrument. It is for each of us to know the keys and stops, that we may draw forth the harmonies that lie sleeping in the silent octaves.</text>
<authby>Anonymous</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>If evil be said of thee, and if it be true, correct thyself; if it be a lie, laugh at it.</text>
<authby>Epictetus</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>In many things it is not well to say, "Know thyself"; it is better to say, "Know others." </text>
<authby>Menander</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>The less people speak of their greatness, the more we think of it.</text>
<authby>Lord Bacon</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>He who sedulously attends, pointedly asks, calmly speaks, coolly answers and ceases when he has no more to say is in possession of some of the best requisites of man.</text>
<authby>Johann Casper Lavater</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Men are more mindful of wrongs than of benefits.</text>
<authby>Proverb</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>A good word is an easy obligation; but not to speak ill requires only our silence; which costs us nothing.</text>
<authby>John Tillotson</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>It requires less character to discover the faults of others than is does to tolerate them.</text>
<authby>J. Petit Senn</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Do not forget small kindnesses and do not remember small faults.</text>
<authby>Chinese Proverb</authby>
</quote></quotes>