<quotes><topic>Destiny Quotations</topic>
<quote>
<text>You are what your deep, driving desire is. As your desire is, so is your will. As your will is, so is your deed. As your deed is, so is your destiny.</text>
<authby>Brihadaranyaka Upanishad IV 4.5</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>If we would see the color of our future, we must look for it in our present; if we would gaze on the star of our destiny, we must look for it in our hearts. </text>
<authby>Canon Farrar</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Everywhere man blames nature and fate, yet his fate is mostly but the echo of his character and passions, his mistakes and weaknesses.</text>
<authby>Democritus</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Love nothing but that which comes to you woven in the pattern of your destiny. For what could more aptly fit your needs?</text>
<authby>Marcus Aurelius</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>It is a mistake to look too far ahead. Only one link of the chain of destiny can be handled at a time. </text>
<authby>Winston Churchill</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Adapt yourself to the life you have been given; and truly love the people with whom destiny has surrounded you.</text>
<authby>Marcus Aurelius</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Happy is the man who can do only one thing; in doing it, he fulfills his destiny.</text>
<authby>Joseph Joubert</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Let us follow our destiny, ebb and flow. Whatever may happen, we master fortune by accepting it.</text>
<authby>Virgil</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>The destiny of man is in his own soul.</text>
<authby>Herodotus</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Our destiny can be examined, but it cannot be justified or totally explained. We are simply here.</text>
<authby>Iris Murdoch</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>The acts of this life are the destiny of the next. </text>
<authby>Eastern Proverb</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Every man has his own destiny; the only imperative is to follow it, to accept it, no matter where it leads him.</text>
<authby>Henry Miller</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>The tissue of life to be we weave with colors all our own, And in the field of destiny we reap as we have sown.</text>
<authby>John Greenleaf Whittier</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>There is a divinity that shapes our ends, Rough-hew them how we will. </text>
<authby>William Shakespeare</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Our destiny changes with our thoughts; we shall become what we wish to become, do what we wish to do, when our habitual thoughts correspond with our desires.</text>
<authby>Orison Swett Marden</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>A man's happiness or unhappiness depends as much on his temperament as on his destiny.</text>
<authby>Francois de La Rochefoucauld</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Destiny is not a matter of chance; but a matter of choice. It is not a thing to be waited for, It is a thing to be acheived.</text>
<authby>William Jennings Bryan</authby>
</quote></quotes>