<quotes><topic>Experience Quotations</topic>
<quote>
<text>It is good to learn what to avoid by studying the misfortunes of others. </text>
<authby>Publius Syrius</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>If you would know the road ahead, ask someone who has traveled it.</text>
<authby>Chinese Proverb</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Experience is by industry achieved, And perfected by the swift course of time. </text>
<authby>William Shakespeare</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Experience keeps a dear school, but fools will learn in no other.</text>
<authby>Benjamin Franklin</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Nothing is a waste of time if you use the experience wisely.</text>
<authby>François Auguste René Rodin</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>The education of circumstances is superior to that of tuition.</text>
<authby>William Wordsworth</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Experience is a grindstone; and it is lucky for us, if we can get brightened by it, and not ground. </text>
<authby>Josh Billings</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Knowledge gained through experience is far superior and many times more useful than bookish knowledge. </text>
<authby>Mahatma Gandhi</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>The experience of others adds to our knowledge, but not to our wisdom; that is dearer bought.</text>
<authby>Hosea Ballou</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>All truly wise thoughts have been thought already, thousands of times; but to make them truly ours, we must think them over again honestly, until they take firm root in our personal experience.</text>
<authby>Johann Wolfgang von Goethe</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>He knows the water best who has waded through it.</text>
<authby>Danish Proverb</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>The years teach much which the days never know.</text>
<authby>Ralph Waldo Emerson</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Those who come last enter with advantage. They are born to the wealth of antiquity. The materials for judging are prepared, and the foundations of knowledge are laid to their hands. Besides, if the point was tried by antiquity, antiquity would lose it, for the present age is really the oldest, and has the largest experience to plead.</text>
<authby>Collier</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>All experience is an arch to build upon.</text>
<authby>Henry Brook Adams</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Experience is a jewel, and it had need be so, for it is often purchased at an infinite rate.</text>
<authby>William Shakespeare</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Experience is a safe light to walk by, and he is not a rash man who expects to succeed in future from the same means which have secured it in times past.</text>
<authby>Wendell Phillips</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Pick up a grain a day and add to your heap. You will soon learn, by happy experience, the power of littles as applied to intellectual processes and gains. </text>
<authby>John S. Hart</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>That learning which thou gettest by thy own observation and experience, is far beyond that which thou gettest by precept; as the knowledge of a traveler exceeds that which is got by reading.</text>
<authby>Thomas à Kempis</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>A moment's insight is sometimes worth a life's experience.</text>
<authby>Oliver Wendall Holmes</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Experience is not what happens to a man: it is what a man does with what happens to him.</text>
<authby>Aldous Huxley</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Experience is the universal mother of sciences.</text>
<authby>Miguel de Cervantes</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>da Vinci portrait : Experience does not err; only your judgments err by expecting from her what is not in her power.</text>
<authby>Lenoardo da Vinci</authby>
</quote></quotes>