<quotes><topic>Fear of Failure</topic>
<quote>
<text>Go back a little to leap further. </text>
<authby>John Clarke</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>It is hard to fail, but it is worse never to have tried to succeed.</text>
<authby>Theodore Roosevelt</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Half of the failures in life come from pulling one's horse when he is leaping.</text>
<authby>Thomas Hood</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>I failed my way to success.</text>
<authby>Thomas Edison</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Our doubts are traitors, and make us lose the good we oft might win, by fearing to attempt.</text>
<authby>William Shakespeare</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Every failure brings with it the seed of an equivalent success.</text>
<authby>Napoleon Hill</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Failure is blindness to the strategic element in events; success is readiness for instant action when the opportune moment arrives. </text>
<authby>Newell D. Hillis</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>They fail, and they alone, who have not striven. </text>
<authby>Thomas Bailey Aldrich</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>We learn wisdom from failure much more than success. We often discover what we will do, by finding out what we will not do.</text>
<authby>Samuel Smiles</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>I was never afraid of failure, for I would sooner fail than not be among the best.</text>
<authby>John Keats</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>He that is down needs fear no fall.</text>
<authby>John Bunyan</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Never let the fear of striking out get in your way.</text>
<authby>George Herman "Babe" Ruth</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>One who fears failure limits his activities. Failure is only the opportunity to more intelligently begin again.</text>
<authby>Henry Ford</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Failure is the foundation of success; success is the lurking place of failure.</text>
<authby>Lao-tzu</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Only those who dare to fail greatly can ever achieve greatly.</text>
<authby>John F. Kennedy</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>The greatest mistake you can make in life is to continually be afraid you will make one.</text>
<authby>Elbert Hubbard</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Failure is a trickster with a keen sense of irony and cunning. It takes great delight in tripping one when success is almost within reach.</text>
<authby>Napoleon Hill</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Our greatest glory consist not in never falling, but in rising every time we fall.</text>
<authby>Oliver Goldsmith</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>What would life be if we had no courage to attempt anything?</text>
<authby>Vincent van Gogh</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Bad times have a scientific value. These are occasions a good learner would not miss.</text>
<authby>Ralph Waldo Emerson</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>The greatest men sometimes overshoot themselves, but then their very mistakes are so many lessons of instruction. </text>
<authby>Tom Browne</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>A man of character finds a special attractiveness in difficulty, since it is only by coming to grips with difficulty that he can realize his potentialities.</text>
<authby>Charles de Gaulle</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Experience teaches slowly, and at the cost of mistakes.</text>
<authby>James A. Froude</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>The only people who never fail are those who never try.</text>
<authby>Ilka Chase</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>It is the want of diligence, rather than the want of means, that causes most failures.</text>
<authby>Alfred Mercier</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>A man's life is interesting primarily when he has failed--I well know. For it's a sign that he tried to surpass himself.</text>
<authby>Georges Clemenceau</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>He who fears being conquered is sure of defeat.</text>
<authby>Napoleon Bonaparte</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>There is no failure except in no longer trying.</text>
<authby>Elbert Hubbard</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>There is no impossibility to him who stands prepared to conquer every hazard. The fearful are the failing.</text>
<authby>Sarah J. Hale</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Disappointments are to the soul what thunderstorms are to the air.</text>
<authby>Johann C. F. von Schiller</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Failure teaches success.</text>
<authby>Japanese Saying</authby>
</quote></quotes>
