<quotes><topic>Follow Your Dreams</topic>
<quote>
<text>I have spread my dreams beneath your feet. Tread softly because you tread on my dreams.</text>
<authby>W.B. Yeats</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Go confidently in the direction of your dreams. Live the life you have imagined.</text>
<authby>Henry David Thoreau</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Every great dream begins with a dreamer. Always remember, you have within you the strength, the patience, and the passion to reach for the stars to change the world.</text>
<authby>Harriet Tubman</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Reach high, for stars lie hidden in your soul. Dream deep, for every dream precedes the goal.</text>
<authby>Pamela Vaull Starr</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>It is precisely the possibility of realizing a dream that makes life interesting.</text>
<authby>Paulo Coelho, The Alchemist</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>All men dream but not equally. Those who dream by night in the dusty recesses of their minds wake in the day to find that it was vanity; but the dreamers of the day are dangerous men, for they may act their dream with open eyes to make it possible.</text>
<authby>T.E. Lawrence</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Our truest life is when we are in dreams awake.</text>
<authby>Henry David Thoreau</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>So often times it happens that we live our lives in chains And we never even know we have the key.</text>
<authby>Lyrics from Already Gone, peformed by the Eagles for their 1974 On the Border album</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>The end of wisdom is to dream high enough not to lose the dream in the seeking of it.</text>
<authby>William Faulkner</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>I like the dreams of the future better than the history of the past.</text>
<authby>Patrick Henry</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>No one has ever achieved anything from the smallest to the greatest unless the dream was dreamed first.</text>
<authby>Laura Ingalls Wilder</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Hold fast to dreams, for if dreams die, life is a broken winged bird that cannot fly.</text>
<authby>Lanston Hughes</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>The future belongs to those who believe in the beauty of their dreams.</text>
<authby>Eleanor Roosevelt</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Not to dream boldly may turn out to be simply irresponsible.</text>
<authby>George Leonard</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Commitment leads to action. Action brings your dream closer. </text>
<authby>Marcia Wieder</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Dreams are the touchstones of our character.</text>
<authby>Henry David Thoreau</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>The question for each man to settle is not what he would do if he had means, time, influence and educational advantages; the question is what he will do with the things he has. The moment a young man ceases to dream or to bemoan his lack of opportunities and resolutely looks his conditions in the face, and resolves to change them, he lays the corner-stone of a solid and honorable success.</text>
<authby>Hamilton Wright Mabie</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>The best way to make your dreams come true is to wake up.</text>
<authby>Paul Valery </authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>A skillful man reads his dreams for self-knowledge, yet not the details but the quality.</text>
<authby>Ralph Waldo Emerson</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Our waking hours form the text of our lives, our dreams, the commentary.</text>
<authby>Anonymous</authby>
</quote><quote>
<text>Hope is the dream of the waking man.</text>
<authby>French Proverb</authby>
</quote></quotes>
